Takeshi Ishikawa

Full Stack Blockchain Engineer

Fukuoka, Japan takeshi028@outlook.com

ABOUT ME

Takeshi is a full-stack developer with a strong focus on blockchain. Familiar with all categories of decentralized finance (DeFi) protocols and passionate about all things blockchain. He has experience with full-stack web development and, working directly with clients, managing small engineering teams.

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, TypeScript
React, Next, Gatsby, Vue, Nuxt, React Native
Bootstrap, Tailwind Css, Material UI, Antd
Node.js, Express, Strapi, PHP, Python
MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Amazon DynamoDB
Solidity, Smart Contract, Hardhat, Truffle, Web3.js, Ether.js, Stacks, Ordinal
Moralis, Infura, Alchemy, Ethereum, BSC, Avalanche, Polygon, Solana
AWS, GCP, CI/CD, Git, Docker, Chat GPT

EXPERIENCE

Aqualis DAO - Blockchain Engineer

Oct 2022

- Cloned Aave Liquidity Protocol contracts and libraries.
- Contributed to Aqualis Staking, Lending Protocol contract developments.
- Built Aqualis DeFI MVP using React/Next.js, Web3.js and AWS Serverless API.
- Technologies: Solidity, DeFi, Hardhat, Lending, Next.js, AWS, Web3.js

Phantom Network (PxN) - Full-Stack Engineer

Nov 2022 - Feb 2023

- Developed the leading online platform for purchasing goods with cryptocurrency.
- Implemented payment gateway, shipping method, and express checkout. I also worked on the customer profile customization page.
- Technologies: React, Next.js, Web3, Ethers, AWS

NEX10 LABS - Full-Stack Engineer

Mar 2022 - Aug 2022

- Developed NFT, Staking and Upgradable Proxy contracts.
- Worked on Nex10 Marketplace project which sells NFT, Physical Items into CryptoCurrency.
- Implemented Next.js/React-based app hosted and integrated Staking, Marketplace contracts.
- Technologies: Next.js, MongoDB, AWS S3, Web3, Ethers, CI/CD

Divvy.Bet - Technical Advisor | Lead

Oct 2021 - Jan 2022

- Advising a small startup to attempt to disrupt the vulnerability and bug bounty space.
- Helped guide direction, acquire clients, and advise on company direction.
- I was responsible for the integration of crypto betting and third-party APIs for sports.
- Technologies: React, Go, Graphql, Web3, Solana, Rust, Antd

Don-key Finance - Blockchain Developer

May 2021 - Oct 2021

- Developed DON governance token, Staking and Bridge contracts.
- Implemented User authentication by user wallet signature.
- Worked on the styling of React components along with Styled-components.
- Developed Graphql endpoints for community features.
- Technologies: React, Typescript, Gatsby, Node, Web3, Solidity, DynamoDB

LegalTechnology Hub - Front-End Developer

Apr 2020 - Mar 2021

- Built beautiful and mobile responsive UI components in Vue js.
- Fixed mobile responsive issue on server-side rendering in Nuxt.js using JavaScript packages such as Simple-Calendar.
- Technologies: Vue, Nuxt.js, Vuetify, Strapi, CI/CD, GCP

Ethernity.live - Full-Stack Developer

Feb 2019 - May 2020

- Developed Chess and RPS(Rock paper scissors) games based on BTC.
- Implemented mobile-responsive front-end pages with React, Bootstrap, and SCSS.
- Developed and deployed Solidity contracts on Ethereum blockchain.
- Developed back-end APIs using Node.js.
- Tracked and fixed existing system issues using Trello as a reporting tool.
- Technologies: React, Vue, PHP, BTC, Web3, CI/CD, GCP, AWS

Fukuoka Software Development Co.,Ltd. - Full-Stack Developer

Aug 2016 - Dec 2018

 Worked on Influencer marketing and E-commerce projects as a full-stack developer.

- Developed Rest APIs using Node.js, PHP/Laravel, Python/Django.
- Implemented reusable and complex UI components with Javascript frameworks.
- Technologies: Javascript, Typescript, PHP, Python, SQL, SASS, Docker

PORTFOLIO

Grey Market

https://gm.co/

React, Next.js, Web3, Solidity, AWS DynamoDB, DigitalOcean

Don-key Finance

https://don-key.finance/

Solidity, Web3, DeFi, Staking, Bridge, React, Gatsby, Three.js, Strapi

Divvy

https://divvy.bet/

Solana, Sports Betting, React, Rust, Antd, GCP

Legaltech Hub

https://www.legaltechnologyhub.com/

Vue, Nuxt.js, Typescript, Vuetify, AWS

EDUCATION

Fukuoka Institute of Technology

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science 2012 - 2016